<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE quotations>
<quotations>

<quote author="H.L. Mencken">
    Evil is that which one believes of others.  It is a sin to believe evil
    of others, but it is seldom a mistake.
</quote>

<quote author="Geoffrey James" reference="The Tao of Programming">
    <line>A well-used door needs no oil on its hinges.</line>
    <line>A swift-flowing steam does not grow stagnant.</line>
    <line>Neither sound nor thoughts can travel through a vacuum.</line>
    <line>Software rots if not used.</line>
    <line/>
    <line>These are great mysteries.</line>
</quote>

<quote author="Martin Mull">
    Show business is just like high school, except you get paid.
</quote>

<quote author="Stephen Pile" reference="The Book of Heroic Failures">
    <heading>The Least Successful Executions</heading>
    <p>
    History has furnished us with two executioners worthy of attention.
    The first performed in Sydney in Australia.  In 1803 three attempts
    were made to hang a Mr. Joseph Samuels.  On the first two of these the
    rope snapped, while on the third Mr. Samuels just hung there peacefully
    until he and everyone else got bored.  Since he had proved
    unsusceptible to capital punishment, he was reprieved.
    </p>
    <p>
    The most important British executioner was Mr. James Berry who tried
    three times in 1885 to hang Mr. John Lee at Exeter Jail, but on each
    occasion failed to get the trap door open.
    </p>
    <p>
    In recognition of this achievement, the Home Secretary commuted Lee's
    sentence to "life" imprisonment.  He was released in 1917, emigrated
    to America and lived until 1933.
    </p>
</quote>

<quote author="the Dalai Lama">
    If you can, help others.  If you can't, at least don't hurt others.
</quote>

<quote author="Alfred Hitchcock">
    Television has brought back murder into the home -- where it belongs.
</quote>

<quote author="Abraham Lincoln">
    I don't know who my grandfather was; I am much more concerned to know
    what his grandson will be.
</quote>

</quotations>
